So the first thing that we're going to be doing with Microsoft Designer is creating images, you know.
So how it works is that you basically give it a prompt and you'll get your image out of it, you know.
So I click on images and as you see, we'll be forwarded to the image creator, you know, in the URL.
And I wait.
And as you see, I'm forwarded to the image creator of Microsoft Designer.
So it says create an image, describe your image, describe what you want to create, and this size, you know.
So it says over here, it says as you see, you have credits, use them to create, and if I click on get more credits, yeah, we have 15 credits over here as well as you see.
And yeah, so this is how Microsoft Designer works. Basically, it also has a paid option.
So how you pay it is by buying more credits, you know, something like that.
So whatever, we're limited one or three.
That's all that I wanted to say.
And what happened?
So let me reload this page.
Yes.